Guide to Speeches in the Records of the Office of the President (Dr. John Brademas) RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Farewell to Dean Redlich, 31 May 1988 (Box 622, Folder 57)
  - Introductory remarks on an exhibit lent by the Benaki Museum, NYU, June 1988 (Box 622, Folder 58)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring Guggenheim Fellows, 1 June 1988 (Box 622, Folder 59)
  - Remarks & script for NYU commencement, 2 June 1988 (Box 622, Folder 60)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, NYU, 2 June 1988 (Box 622, Folder 61)
  - Reception for Dean Howard Newman, NYU, 15 June 1988 (Box 622, Folder 63)
  - Remarks on receiving an award from the Greek Orthodox Archdiocese (Boston, MA), 6 July 1988 (Box 622, Folder 64)
  - Remarks on college athletics before the Education Daily Consensus Panel, NYU, 7 July 1988 (Box 622, Folder 65)
  - Washington Workshops, 10 July 1988 (Box 622, Folder 66)
  - Blurb for the Vulnerable, NYU, 13 July 1988 (Box 622, Folder 67)
  - Address to Sigma Xi, NYU, 13 July 1988 (Box 622, Folder 68)
  - Introduction of Mario Cuomo and Michael Dukakis, NYU, 11 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 69)
  - Upward Bound luncheon and graduation, NYU, 12 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 70)
  - Letter to Kenneth Jon Rose, 12 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 71)
  - Introduction to a book on political science, 14 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 72)
  - Introductory remarks, How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, NYU, 14 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 73)
  - Notes on leadership, 14 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 74)
  - Essay on liberal education, 17 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 75)
  - Remarks on student aid delivered at Lehman College, 23 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 76)
  - Comments on "Mike Dukakis on the Issues: College Opportunity", 25 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 77)
  - Letter to Janet Kerr-Tener, Ph.D., 25 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 78)
  - NYU Magazine, letter for the President), 30 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 79)
  - Dedication of Sidney & Sarah Brown Study Center, Vanderbilt Hall, 30 August 1988 (Box 622, Folder 80)
  - School of Law Faculty Luncheon, 1 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 81)
  - Foreword for The Presidency in American Politics, 1 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 82)
  - Student Convocation, NYU, 6 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 83)
  - Statement in support of Dukakis, 7 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 84)
  - Talking points for remarks made at a meeting of the Board of Regents, NYU, 8 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 85)
  - Review of Jill Krementz's manuscript, 12 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 86)
  - Review of Dr. Stratigos' manuscript, 12 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 87)
  - Letter to Harold Brown on Congress and foreign policy, 19 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 88)
  - Suggested response to George Bull, 20 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 90)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 22 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 91)
  - Harold Weill Medal Presentation Dinner, NYU, 26 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 92)
  - Reception for new graduate students, NYU, 27 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 93)
  - Remarks by Dr. Brademas and Mr. Tisch at a convocation and dinner honoring Francois Mitterrand, NYU, 28 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 94)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at the Women's Campaign Fund Dinner (NYC), 29 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 95)
  - Briefing for Rhodes Scholars, NYU, 30 September 1988 (Box 622, Folder 96)
  - Remarks on Japanese-U.S. relations in the post-Reagan era delivered before the Graduate School of Business Administration Conference on Japan/US Relations, NYU, 3 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 97)
  - "Education & The Nation's Agenda: Perspectives in an Election Year," Beta Gamma Sigma Alumni, NYU, 3 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 98)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Dinner (NYC), 4 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 99)
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business press conference, 6 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 100)
  - Address, American Council for the Arts Conference (New Brunswick, NJ), 7 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 101)
  - Remarks delivered at a celebration and dinner honoring Georgakis & Vryonis, NYU, 10 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 103)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a Stern School of Business Board of Overseers Dinner, NYU, 18 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 104)
  - Art & Business Council Luncheon (NYC), 20 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 105)
  - Reception for Martin Luther King Scholars, NYU, 20 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 106)
  - All-University Convocation, NYU, 20 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 107)
  - Annual Archbishop Iakovos Feast Day Dinner (Washington, D.C.), 22 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 108)
  - Remarks at dinner honoring Graduate School of Public Administration Dean Newman, NYU, 24 October 1988 (Box 622, Folder 109)
  - Campaign for Oxford convocation (Oxford, England), 26 October 1988 (Box 623, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254741
  - National Arts Club Dinner honoring William Passannante, 26 October 1988 (Box 623, Folder 2)
  - Allan Bloom rebuttal, 28 October 1988 (Box 623, Folder 3)
  - "Education for a Strong & Secure America: An Election-Eve Perspective," delivered before the Woman's National Democratic Club (Washington, D.C.), 31 October 1988 (Box 623, Folder 4)
  - Post-election thoughts on the new president and education, 8 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 5)
  - Remarks delivered before a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 10 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 6)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts & Letters, NYU, 14 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 7)
  - NYU Opportunity Fellows Reception, 14 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 8)
  - 1st Liberty Forum Luncheon, 15 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 9)
  - Education Daily Consensus Panel, 15 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 10)
  - Trustees Scholars Dinner, NYU, 16 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles Alumni Reception, 21 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 12)
  - 1988 Axios Man of the Year Award (Los Angeles, CA), 22 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 13)
  - "Excellence & Opportunity: Challenges to the Modern University," delivered at a seminar on quality and efficiency of higher education sponsored by the Economic Development Institute of the World Bank (Brasilia, Brazil), 27 November 1988 (Box 623, Folder 14)
  - "The Vision of Hubert Humphrey: Education for a Better Tomorrow," 10th Anniversary Hubert Humphrey Fellowship Speech (Rio de Janeiro, Brazil), 1 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 15)
  - Reception celebration the publication of America in Theory, NYU, 5 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Service Reception, NYU, 5-7 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 17)
  - Introduction of Dan Rostenkowski at a conference on taxation (NYC), 6 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 18)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 8 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 20)
  - Arthur L. Carter Hall Dedication, 12 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 21)
  - Remarks at a dinner honoring Mr. and Mrs. Stern, NYU, 13 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 23)
  - Lecture by Speros Vryonis on the 900th anniversary of St. John Monastery (NYC), 13 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 24)
  - Testimony delivered at a hearing of the Joint Subcommittee on Education and Health (Washington, D.C.), 14 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, 15 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 26)
  - Issues in the 101st Congress, NYU, 21 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 27)
  - Politics of Education, 21 December 1988 (Box 623, Folder 28)
  - Letter bidding farewell to Father Rafferty, NYU, 11 January 1989 (Box 623, Folder 29)
  - Remarks delivered at the annual meeting of the American Council on Education (San Diego, CA), 20 January 1989 (Box 623, Folder 30)
  - Eagleton response to Harold Brown document, 20 January 1989 (Box 623, Folder 31)
  - Remarks announcing a gift from the Tisches at a press conference for the Medical Center, NYU, 25 January 1989 (Box 623, Folder 32)
  - NYU Alumni Reception in Atlanta, 27 January 1989 (Box 623, Folder 33)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Dinner, NYU, 30 January 1989 (Box 623, Folder 35)
  - Committee of the Year 2000 meeting (NYC), 31 January 1989 (Box 623, Folder 36)
  - "An Olive Branch Within Easy Reach", February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 37)
  - "The Arts and Their Teaching: Prospects and Problems," delivered at the Getty Center for Education in the Arts National Conference (Los Angeles, CA), 2 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 38)
  - Essay on Berlin and New York, 3 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 39)
  - Robert Wood Johnson press conference, NYU, 6 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 40)
  - McGeorge Bundy book reception, NYU, 6 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 42)
  - Remarks on student loan default problems, NYU, 8 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 43)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 9 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 44)
  - Remarks on receiving the Hellene of the Year Award at the Athenian Ball (NYC), 15 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 45)
  - Informal remarks delivered at the Faculty of Arts and Science Board of Overseers Meeting, NYU, 16 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 46)
  - "Education for a Strong & Sure America," delivered at the Mid-Atlantic Club Luncheon, 16 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 47)
  - Interview of Dr. Brademas broadcast on FNN, 22 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 48)
  - Talking points for remarks made at a reception for the President's Council, 22 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 49)
  - Essay, "The Challenge of International Education," published in the Journal of International Affairs, 22 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 50)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a reception honoring the United Way and NYU Community Fund Campaign, 23 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 51)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring the Comptroller General, NYU, 27 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 52)
  - Talking points for remarks made at NYU Day in Albany, 28 February 1989 (Box 623, Folder 53)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon (NYC), 1 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 54)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a breakfast honoring the NYC Partnership/Urban Research Center, NYU, 2 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 55)
  - Remarks delivered before potential undergraduate candidates, NYU, 5 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 57)
  - Informal remarks delivered at a meeting of the Alumni Council, NYU, 8 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 58)
  - Brief remarks preceding the Ramasco Lecture in the Department of History, NYU, 9 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 59)
  - Introductory remarks at the Aphrodisisas Colloquium, NYU, 9 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 60)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 9 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 61)
  - Introductory remarks, 22nd Annual Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (NYC), 15 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 63)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, 23 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 64)
  - 4th Annual Petrie Lecture in Entrepreneurship, NYU, 28 March 1988 (Box 623, Folder 65)
  - Keynote address, Association of American Publishers Annual Meeting (Boca Raton, FL), 30 March 1989 (Box 623, Folder 66)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon commemorating the enthronement of Archbishop Iakovos (NYC), 2 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 67)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Lee Hamilton, NYU, 3 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 68)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner hosted by David Kriser, NYU, 5 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 70)
  - Presidential Scholars Reception, NYU, 8 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 71)
  - Annenberg Program Debate, NYU, 10 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 72)
  - Rudin Reception, NYU, 11 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 73)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at an NYU alumni reception (CT), 12 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 74)
  - Remarks delivered at a reception honoring Chinua Achebe, NYU, 13 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 75)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 13 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 76)
  - "Books, Babies, and Libraries: Making the Connection," delivered at a conference at the New York Public Library, 13 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 77)
  - "The Role of Religion in the Formation of Public Officials: A Theoretical Perspective," delivered at a panel discussion on religion and public policy at Georgetown University (Washington, D.C.), 14 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 78)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the Northeastern Association of Graduate Schools (Albany, NY), 14 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 79)
  - Remarks delivered at a Law School Revue, NYU, 14 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 80)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, NYU, 16 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 81)
  - Laudatio of the Honorable J. William Fulbright (Athens, Greece), 20 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 82)
  - Article for NYU Advances, 21 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 83)
  - Statement delivered before the Subcommittee on Energy & Water Development of the House Committee on Appropriations (Washington, D.C.), 21 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 84)
  - Statement delivered before the Subcommittee on Natural Resources, Agriculture, Research, & the Environment of the House Committee on Science, Space, and Technology (Washington, D.C.), 21 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 85)
  - Brief remarks at the Conference on Abused Children (NYC), 27 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 86)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a reception honoring E.L. Doctorow, NYU, 27 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 87)
  - Remarks delivered at the NYU Metropolitan Studies Conference on Children, 28 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 88)
  - "The Generational Contract: Educating All Our Youngsters for the 1990s," delivered at the Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching/Americans for Generational Equity Regional Conference, 28 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 89)
  - Remarks delivered at the Washington Square Arch 100th Anniversary Celebration, 30 April 1989 (Box 623, Folder 90)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science Too Important To Be Left to Scientists?" ( Nexus article), May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 91)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Robert Maxwell, NYU, 1 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 92)
  - Advances at NYU, 2 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 93)
  - CASH Luncheon, NYU, 2 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 94)
  - Remarks delivered at a taping of Author, Author by Dean Harvey Stedman, 2 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 95)
  - Remarks delivered at a School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions Prism Award luncheon honoring Robert Maxwell, 3 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 96)
  - Remarks at a meeting of the Alumni Council, NYU, 3 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 97)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 4 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 98)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a dinner honoring the Greek Press of the Diaspora, NYU, 6 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 99)
  - "Some Social Implications of New Technologies," Omni Desk Conference, NYU, 8 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 100)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at the presentation of the 25-Year Service Awards, NYU, 11 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 103)
  - Remarks delivered at a reception celebrating the Tisch School of the Arts, 11 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 104)
  - NYU Community Fund, 16 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 105)
  - Remarks delivered at the Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, NYU, 17 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 106)
  - Script for Medical Center Commencement, NYU, 18 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 107)
  - Alumni Commencement Breakfast, NYU, 18 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 108)
  - Remarks delivered at a ceremony honoring Albert Gallatin Medalist Taggart Whipple, 18 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 109)
  - Remarks delivered at NYU commencement, 18 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 110)
  - Script for the 157th Commencement Exercises, NYU, 18 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 111)
  - "Reflections on Congress," delivered at the White Burkett Miller Center of Public Affairs at the University of Virginia, 19 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 112)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at the Brasenose College Charitable Foundation Dinner, NYU, 30 May 1989 (Box 623, Folder 113)
  - Remarks delivered at the Herbert R. Silverman Scholarship Fund Reception, NYU, 1 June 1989 (Box 623, Folder 114)
  - Wayne E. Hirschkorn Memorial Fund Reception, NYU, 6 June 1989 (Box 623, Folder 117)
  - Remarks delivered at a reception commemorating a cultural & educational agreement between the U.S. & Spain (Washington, D.C.), 7 June 1989 (Box 623, Folder 118)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a breakfast meeting of theGallatin Associates & President's Council, NYU, 7 June 1989 (Box 623, Folder 119)
  - Statement for press kit, Archivists Round Table of Metropolitan New York, 13 June 1989 (Box 623, Folder 120)
  - Brief remarks delivered at the NYU/Yugoslavia Marketing Seminar (Yugoslavia), 16 June 1989 (Box 623, Folder 121)
  - "Higher Education in the 1990s: Prospects & Problems," delivered at the Gannett Center Conference, 18 June 1989 (Box 623, Folder 122)
  - Remarks delivered at a Medical Center faculty meeting, NYU, 19 June 1989 (Box 624, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254709
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Pascual Maragall, NYU, 21 June 1989 (Box 624, Folder 2)
  - Article in Oxford Today, 23 June 1989 (Box 624, Folder 3)
  - Remarks delivered at a Silver Shalis cruise hosted by Larry & Klara Silverstein, 28 June 1989 (Box 624, Folder 4)
  - Nomination of Marian Wright Edelman for McGraw-Hill Prize, NYU, 30 June 1989 (Box 624, Folder 5)
  - Letter to the Honorable Terry Sanford regarding an agenda for higher education, 5 July 1989 (Box 624, Folder 6)
  - Response to Newsday editorial on forgiveness/scholarship payback, 6 July 1989 (Box 624, Folder 7)
  - Funding for fairness, 2 August 1989 (Box 624, Folder 8)
  - Introduction to Medical Center brochure, 22 August 1989 (Box 624, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Convocation, NYU, 5 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 10)
  - Remarks delivered at the NYC mayoral candidate debates, NYU, 6 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 11)
  - Op-ed piece on drugs, 6 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 12)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the Community Service Society Retired Senior Volunteer Program, 14 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 14)
  - Introduction of Senator Moynihan at NAICU Leadership Conference, NYU, 14 September 1990 (Box 624, Folder 15)
  - Caldwell College 50th Anniversary Convocation (Caldwell, NJ), 20 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 17)
  - Covenant of Peace Award Dinner (NYC), 20 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 18)
  - Dedication of the Henry Viscardi High School (Albertson, NY), 21 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 19)
  - Hagop Kevorkian Center Cultural Heritage Conference, NYU, 21 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 20)
  - World Management Congress, NYU, 21 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 21)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring the inauguration of the 47th president of Georgetown University (Washington, D.C.), 23 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 22)
  - Remarks at a press conference announcing the naming of the Robert F. Wagner Graduate School for Public Service, NYU, 25 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 23)
  - Memorial Service for Sidney Hook, NYU, 25 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 24)
  - Tokyo Broadcasting System Luncheon, NYU, 26 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Relations Program Reception, NYU, 26 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 26)
  - New Graduate Students Reception, NYU, Sep 27, 1989 (Box 624, Folder 27)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, NYU, 27 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 28)
  - IRTF Benefit Dinner (NYC), 28 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 29)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring Jorge Semprun, NYU, 29 September 1989 (Box 624, Folder 30)
  - Remarks at a Humanities Council event featuring readings on Greenwich Village, NYU, 3 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 31)
  - Remarks delivered before a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 5 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 32)
  - Remarks preceding the Luce Professorship Inaugural Lecture, NYU, 5 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 33)
  - Remarks delivered at various events commemorating a visit by President Vassiliou of Cyprus, NYU, 5 October 1988 (Box 624, Folder 34)
  - Remarks delivered at a reception and dinner honoring the UAA Presidents, NYU, 11 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 36)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a meeting of the Alumni Council, NYU, 11 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 37)
  - New Jersey Regional Alumni Reception (Short Hills, NJ), 12 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 38)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Luncheon Honoring Soviet Filmmakers, Bobst, (JB Talking Points), 17 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 40)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a reception to inaugurate the Arthur Imperatore Professorship, NYU, 30 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 41)
  - Remarks delivered at the announcement of a campaign for the Real Estate Institute, NYU, 31 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 42)
  - Talking points for remarks made at a dinner honoring Senator Ralph Marino, NYU, 31 October 1989 (Box 624, Folder 43)
  - "The Arts & Politics: Rethinking the American Commitment to Culture," a lecture celebrating the Nancy Hanks Endowment at Duke University (Durham, NC), 2 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 44)
  - Speech given at a forum at Temple Emanu-El, 5 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 45)
  - John Palmer(?), "Preparing for the 21st Century: Perspectives on Public Service, Governance & Global Realities," delivered as part of the Donald MacNaughton Symposium, Syracuse University, 8 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 46)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at the All-University Dinner Dance, NYU, 8 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 47)
  - Report to the University Senate, 9 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 48)
  - Remarks delivered at the dedication of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Room, NYU, 9 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 49)
  - Remarks delivered at the United Hellenic American Congress Dinner Dance (Chicago, IL), 11 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 50)
  - Remarks at the dedication of Onassis Center, NYU, 13 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 51)
  - Trustees Scholars Reception, NYU, 15 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 52)
  - Talking points for remarks at a luncheon honoring CLACS, NYU, 16 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 53)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Mayor Wagner, NYU, 16 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 54)
  - "In Praise of Libraries...," delivered at a luncheon honoring Marie Schwartz, NYU, 17 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 55)
  - Speech before a meeting of the Scholarship Foundation of St. Joseph County (South Bend, IN), 19 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 56)
  - Lecture by Jose Maria Maravall, NYU, 20 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 57)
  - Talking points for remarks announcing a gift to Washington Square Park, 21 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 58)
  - Speech at the 59th annual meeting of the Middle States Association of Collegiate Registrars (Atlantic City, NJ), 27 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 59)
  - "Rebuilding the Public Service," delivered at the Annual Management Conference at the General Accounting Office (Chantilly, VA), 29 November 1989 (Box 624, Folder 60)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the Medical Center Board of Trustees, NYU, 5 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 61)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Elie Wiesel, NYU, 6 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 62)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 7 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 63)
  - Remarks delivered at a memorial service for Dr. Howard A. Rusk, NYU, 7 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 64)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a reception for Ed Koch, Distinguished Visiting Marnold Fellow, NYU, 11 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 65)
  - Education Week interview, 15 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 67)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, 14 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 68)